Two candles, one red, one black
We lit both and laughed at the pact
Mirror cracked, cards on the floor
Who's who you asked?
I'm not sure anymore
You called me devil, I ple-
We're both devils
Steps first, off cliffs without fear
The devil binds what the fool released
And both whisper
Trips the fool wears the crown
No moral here, no clean divide
We're just reflections that switch sides
What are people saying?
I don't understand that. I don't understand.
Where am I?
Okay, here we are.
I'm too drunk to really have a show.
I think I'll just play clips and stuff.
I don't know what to do
She's the baddest of them all.
The baddest of them all.
Is it good or is it bad?
I'm not sure.
Why did I DM you? I'm sorry, Jamie.
I'm like a little bit...
I'm like...
This is all the energy I have.
It's the show right now.
This is literally...
Here
Had to go bathroom
Love not me I'm shadow band again pop pop pop bro mute your mic then boom
Drop a baseline dirtier than the check
Smashing routers like vows, Canada dries, licking watch catalogs somehow.
Rando's ranting bout A.I. Toons, while his playlists all cartoons.
Mason's pacing red outrage, threatening people from an undisclosed stage.
Natalie Benz's back foot behind head, mods praying Lord, not again!
From the bone, Braggs, he just dropped a cosmic load
Alex and his mic, nuclear loud Beat the storms and turn it down, you clown
Tony bombs the stream with skin, chat explodes
Mods dive in, he man in time, rogue and free
Burning bridges, living HD
Authors, they're just smiling sweet Y'all need Jesus or at least some sleep
And it's all so true.
Ghost is connected.
Canada drive timed out.
Randall's still typing.
Wait, did Vita just ban me?
Laughter static cat me out.
In stream noise.
Happy day everyone.
Thank you, you're sweet.
I don't know how good I'll be tonight. I mean, it's like I keep trying to like do a good show and
Let this cooperate with me, but you know what? I'll still try. Oh
Someone come in on stage set. Oh, no, it wasn't the pulse alarm
Okay, well, we'll try again
In the glow of neon, she's cutting the night
A blade in her hand, a fire in her eyes so bright
He shows up in red, with a hose and a grin
The fire is found She laughs like a secret, sharp as a knife
But maybe she's tired of the dangerous life He drops his shirt with a volunteer's pride
He's cold and dirty but he'll learn her name
She's the spark that can't be contained
Can a fireman's heart be the one unchained?
She's a wild card queen, he's a rescue man
To misfit stance, where the story is
Could true love be forged in more than just love?
Oh, that was epic.
I think it was, I think it was.
That was fucking epic.
I'm gonna put that in for nomination.
What up, Psyche?
What's up, Brian? How are you?
Can I drive?
Brad, how are you?
We're all here.
I have another half a beer at least,
and I'm gonna kind of shelf it a while.
Are you drinking tonight?
Canada. Yeah, voodoo rangers.
Canada, are you there?
Are you cutie patootie?
Cutie patootie.
Is he there Canada? I'm thirsty in an airplane. I need some ginger ale. I
Don't even know who that guy is
ginger ale
I don't know. I think he's disconnected. How are you ran? I haven't seen you for a while. I'm good. I'm good. How are you?
It was my birthday yesterday. Everyone say happy birthday. Thank you. Thank you
Happy birthday. Are you 29 years old? No, I'm 26. Oh my gosh, even younger. Okay
You're not gonna be 29 for another 10 years and so enjoy it right?
Okay
Happy birthday. We have always smile Mason the drummer Mason get up here. Thank you psyche. Do I get a birthday reading?
Yeah, you do
I'm a Libra. So yeah, okay your Libra. So your birthday is right around this time
Yep. Yep. Okay. So let's see what we got for I'm gonna post some cards for rain. Here rain
First we got the Wheel of Fortune and so things have been going your favor lately. It's like you
Lately this is like the Wheel of Fortune in your favor. You may have been waiting for a while, but it is in your favor right now
Okay, we also have the star you're getting a lot more attention about something you also can make a wish too
Also, you're giving somebody to the world like a gift to the world
To the world right now. What else we got for rain
Ray and I got this this uh, oh the seven of pentacles says look upon my works
So you've been working hard on something or you're gonna be working hard on something
Yeah, for you you're putting that you're planting the seeds right maybe right now or just growing them and it's like something
That's gonna be really beneficial for you fruitful for you. Yeah
Three of one this is you have left that your castle and are now on the journey on a vast open sea a place of doubt
And in security, a progress is being made.
Okay, so maybe if you don't, you are on a journey
and you're like, oh, it's not happening fast enough.
Something that I want is not coming fast enough.
But it will come and it's like you're making progress
on this whatever journey you're made.
I got one more on this deck.
This one says 10 of wands.
You feel like you're carrying some burdens.
Maybe other people's burdens.
They're not like heavy, but they're like burdensome.
And you can always put them down.
I'm gonna get you one more card from another deck.
Let me see it from this deck.
This is called the make your a magic deck.
Okay, this one says wings.
You can see this one.
She's flying.
It says wings.
It's a fat so.
Says you never did those wings to fly, okay?
You never needed them to fly.
You can already fly, okay?
Yeah.
You never needed those wings, okay?
So whatever, whatever, for something you thought,
oh, I need you to do this.
I need you to understand how to do this
before I can fly, but you can always fly.
I get that message.
So I hope you like it.
Oh my gosh, thank you psyche. I really appreciate it problem
I'll give you a better like a longer reading too if you ask for it
Like I just like I'm a little bit drunk tonight and like it's okay. We can do that later
How's everyone we got Gotti we got rain and we got Canada dry Canada right there yet. No
Kick them off
Yeah, Kim off until he says something you have to come back when you're ready to talk. Okay, there you go. Fix your shit, dude
Don't come up fast
We want psyche show you got to be ready for this shit. Yeah
Yeah, exactly. No amateurs. He's taking a bong
Fifty minute bomb a 15 minute bomb or bomb or what does that mean?
Maybe sniffing his girl's ass. I don't know. Oh my gosh. Okay, Mason. What are you? Have you been fighting with Mason in the chat tonight?
Who Darrell and Mason are going at it right now. Oh
Psyche, you know Wiggins mentioned you in his stream
He was making he was making fun of you for being gay
Wiggins, I don't even know a person named Wiggins. Oh Wiggins that old man with the with the
the girl by his side
Are you talking about like he's like, oh is that old man with like the younger wife and stuff?
Yeah, yeah with the ward on her lip. Yeah making fun of me for being gay
I mean guys, I was like, you know, I let him on my show and I was like had sympathy for that
Yeah, yeah, and he's fucking ungrateful like he's he's fucking making fun of you and shit. Oh my gosh
I'm shocked. Well, you know what if you can make fun of me. Hey, Joanie is Joanie here. Oh, it's Joe Shippley y'all
Oh y'all y'all Wiggins. Yeah
Joe Wiggins. Yeah, what's up with Joni dude? She's like mad at me for no reason
Okay, well, I don't want to give too much away, but I think Joni thought that you were some guy on some other show
Like making fun of her or doxing her or something and she's like she thought that your name was familiar
You're familiar. No, God. He doesn't doc. That doesn't make any sense. I was like, that's not God
He probably I think that's probably somebody else that sounds like him
Hey, Ziggy, you know, it's a sense. Oh
Dude, we're all crossing paths tonight, man. That's
What's going on? Look at fucking look at psyche. He is looking beautiful tonight guys
I got my wig on too. Oh
No, what is this Z what's good, bro? Hey, it's good man. It's an old lady witch wing
Oh, looks like Jen, but she raw not old lady. You're a
Lady
Jen Jen looks like that. Like no
Make it make your face it's like make your face sideways and go what do that
Give us a little valley girl. Oh my god
Oh my god, you should be like arrest me daddy. Hey, got it daddy. Got it
Got it
Hey daddy, yeah, you're hair in your face
No, that's that's gotta call me daddy's dead
No, no, the only person that's going to call him daddy is will here
You should come on with this way too
Vader has a wig
God I see it man. You saw the ace freely. Yeah. Oh, I know
right fucks
Fuck a few weeks ago, and he fucking they took him off life support
them, and
No, he fell. He's like, I'm perfectly fine. Then he fucking falls and then fucking internal bleeding basically rain
Yeah, sucks. They're having a big show in what two months. I think at the White House. It's too bad
Well on a positive. Do you remember Ozfest and all that shit mayhem fest?
Now the now there's a patent on the fucking towing shit where they're taking the fucking
Last show of Ozzy right the title
back to the beginning and they're gonna fucking I
Think they're gonna fucking be doing like a kind of like an Oz first thing again. I think Sharon's gonna do it dude
Fuck fuck. I don't want to see any more Sharon. I'm done with Sharon
I hate Sharon
Fuck if it wasn't for Sharon, dude, if it wasn't for Sharon fucking she she's
Be dead 40 years ago
right
She's a cunt though. I love her. She's the one that created us. She's like, I'm gonna create an artist best
What you guys have
Drop the leg
What is it?
What's Blondie doing? Yeah, yeah drop the link. Yo Z Z. I don't want to say this
But I don't think it's like you like you every time you come up. He leaves. I know
You know, I end up talking about other stuff. So that's you know equal opportunity or just worship him and tell him how beautifully
What if I could see his beautiful blonde hair and I wouldn't you remind me about it? You might be Betty Davis
Yep, Davis
Was yeah psyche come back come on hurry up. What are you doing?
He's probably going to sleep the guys went up all day. I still have that fucking dumb song in my head to that
Oh the funky town on yeah
Did you were were you okay with that like putting gaudy productions in the end of it?
That video it was kind of long, but it was good
the
Fuck I cut it on that backstage. I
Could have done that shirt
Betty David size
Betty David size there you go
Is that really one is that really one JT's backstage. No, that's not Ray
We can't hear anything us like yeah, what are you doing?
Thank you. He's playing mommy dearest come back come back, dude
Thank you. I've seen that face before that looks like Shannon. Oh
Shit it kind of does it does
Is who's that that actor that actually looks familiar that's the guy who played King Tut in Batman
And the Batman show if you get his name Victor something
I don't know
Betty Davis sings I've written a letter to daddy
Hey, Jamie
Jamie
Yeah, what the fuck is going on? I was like is he tweaking again? I thought that was JT. Yeah
He's like he's like I'm sad or something like he put a wig on and he got mad at me. I think
I want him to come back
Wait, why are we where's the host? I know
So I didn't come here to talk to Ziggy
Because I'm the host right now, okay
This is what happened
We got we got Jamie in this, okay
Hey, I keep forgetting Aaron Rodgers place for the Steelers. Yeah, I forget all Steelers
Dumb butters. Hey, listen is August at an NFL game. I don't care
I just have to wait for Prime to start it at 9.30.
Betty Davis.
She was an ugly broad, huh?
Is that what that is?
Yeah, old.
Yeah, me from there.
You're picking on Daryl.
That's all I gotta say.
Are they fighting?
Well, I mean...
Well, they've been fighting for a while.
But that's okay.
You know what?
People know that you're fake well psyche put the blonde wig on and I think
That's funny
Can't put a blonde wig on psyche and never must I
We're watching a movie here the fuck. Yeah, this is the old-school shit. I love that shit
I kind of like that he likes that actually cuz
Yeah, yeah
I fucking like put that into music videos man before like certain things
You guys already do your shout out to like always smile, fake lips, go, see who's in there
People are great aren't they?
Let me see, I'm gonna scroll up
I'm gonna use my lipstick
Oh, that's cool. I didn't know you could do that.
They changed the, you know, they changed that.
Flood?
No, how you can put, you can rearrange like the panelists like that.
Hi.
I'm back.
There it is.
That's all right.
Finally, how are you doing?
J.C. are you there?
I am.
Gaudi.
I know.
Gaudi and Raina.
Guys, we're having the best night ever.
Hey, I just wanted to shout out to HKShay
and Sweet Pea.
Okay, Psyche.
Alright.
I can't see that either of those people in my chat.
They're blocks.
Scowling right now.
I don't pick sides.
I don't pick sides
I do
Nobody what do you mean nobody's mad at you come on
I didn't do anything wrong to Christine. What did I do to Christine? Oh, I like crystal talk talk shit
Why are they mad at you now? I believe in redemptions wanted them. That's why yeah crystal stupid
She is Audi 1k doesn't like crystal dude. She's so stupid. Oh, it's just gonna go
He's a weirdo.
No, that's like, that's Biggie's idol.
What are you talking about?
No, he's a weirdo.
He can't say that.
He's a weirdo.
Don't say that.
He's a beautiful company.
Fuck it.
I'm here all the time, so.
I thought he was a weirdo.
Apparently, you're okay.
Your hero is Crystal.
What's fake teeth? Okay?
Can you do stuff with it
Like you just took Shannon's wig
Is he making fun of our woman right now?
I'm telling you right now you got to tell Gotti. Thanks for saving the fucking show that night because I'll tell you what you mean
Did she almost had you shut down with Hamas chanting?
I know you appreciate it's like
And may say you're fake. I say psyche psyche. I just bought psyche. I just bought my woman a
nice reciprocating saw and
I want you to say like
Remember would be the shit
That Mason isn't really retarded
Wait psyche you like him
You're trying to show everybody that you know
You're not who is no, I don't think so
Exactly what to do to a wrench to
Guys guys let's everybody not argue and and psyche
Hey Jan, I I'm sending you a reciprocating Saul
for your
double-hitter dildo
He looks like the good charlotte lead singer I saw him before in a picture
Daddy did say see me in a picture, but hey Jan, I'm telling you
Right now are you better act straight understand now when you get that reciprocating saw I sent it to you so I also sent you a dildo
And then that way it's reciprocating get it double-headed. You're both in the same time, right?
I have drawings, but I can't play them. I just don't know how to do it. Sorry
You have to share the screen and then put it in the share screen. I'm kidding. I'm kidding
Everybody's joking dude. Yeah
Hey, no, like I just wanted you, you know, I just you know clumsy and gala are my good friends
I could have put that back together, I could have put that back
Because you did that I could have put it back together
Oh, always fighting the pieces of the puzzle
Can't put the pieces back together guys
What somebody lied about having cancer
That is fucking disgusting people are you kidding me?
Yeah, we hate liars
Dude, I have the best aunt in the fucking world bro
We hate the fucking I love I love my aunt man
And she got cancer and didn't know there was four stage and four months after finding out
She's dead don't lie about fucking bullshit like that dude. He's dead never
But you know what?
Clumsy and and God, no, don't say
yeah, clumsy is one of my boys, man.
Not that.
Clumsy.
Clumsy, clairvoyance.
You know what, I was in the psyche, I was in the fuzzy, but then she like kicked me out of her chat, she said go fuck yourself, get out of here.
I could have fixed it, psych, psych, I could have fixed it just a little bit of time for me to fix it.
I know, I know, but if it wasn't going to be fixed, it can't be fixed.
It's okay.
I tried.
Can't be fixed.
Can't be fixed, because she's not.
She's not woman enough
I'm going to go for a W. Who are we talking about?
The only thing the only thing I've the only thing I think is is that like you never make fun of like death
You never make fun of like people with disease and shit like that, you know
And all the women were like, oh my god, oh my we love you
And then they're like, oh, he's taking advantage of you.
Let's all kick out.
Let's all kick psyche in real life.
Well, it looks like that.
He's taking it all the time.
You idiots.
Dumb motherfuckers.
Dummies.
You know what?
This guy looks like a weird, different guy, girl.
You can't be like that in your life.
Dumb, dumb.
Why are they like this?
What's the matter, Meesey?
People say I'm dumb.
you guys are dumb because you're fooled by someone that said they were having cancer and they didn't
no no no you look like a right there when you were in there
let's replace that with reals here
I just said I could have put it together, it would have taken time
it's okay, Jamie, it's okay
well you know how we're all friends and I wanted it to happen
let her talk, no let her talk to him
Yeah, I know
I'm sorry, but it's like you could have talked to me that day and like I'm gonna work it out
And then she blocked me again. So how could I blurk it out?
Jamie, why'd you do that? Not me. I didn't do it. Oh, I think you blocked it. No, I did not
There's no clumsy. There's a lady named Clumsy
I've been here since day one. I'll do that to psych. Well, I'm clumsy
Go Ziggy, would you ever have sex with me in the week?
No, no, I can't I can't do that. Do it if you take the wig off you'd probably do it
Yeah, if you take the wig up all right now
Now you look like
You need about a way you have to do the like left to the right you have to do the left to the right. Yes. There you go
All right, now we're good show your legions to Hitler too and then and then also give a shout out to rain and JT
I'll grab you by the back of your hair
Oh wow, look at this, there he is, what a filthy, it's a CFF party, I just wanted to let you know that ever since the opening of the channel until the end of the channel that we fight all the way through, so I call her one of the adventures, yep, I like it, I don't like him, I don't like him and I like him, it's fucking funny.
Why do you smell? Why does it smell like curry in here?
Why are you fucking Hindustani's here? That's why.
Why does it smell like curry? That's weird.
Curry smells like curry in here.
I love curry.
It smells like shit.
Yeah, it stinks like a possible shit.
I never said that.
I did.
Alright!
Howdy, what are you doing?
Howdy, I want to hear that.
How many talk?
Brusky, brusky.
I'm a lower caste.
Tell me where he lives.
Howdy, what are you doing?
I'm drinking, Ziggy.
No.
I ain't looking anywhere to.
Brusky, brusky.
The question is, where the fuck is Vader?
I told him to come here. He's the one that told me that this was live and
He's not here
Will direct killed Vader
What with what boredom with AIDS
With what boredom
You do it like I do, shut the fuck up.
I wish we could write shows together because then I would like do it like that extra long
I'm gonna do some
No, not today
Okay
Look at this fucking mummy
Oh, put it in the ground
Oh, fuck it
Unwrap that bitch
That bitch boils
I fucking yell at him with fucking skin wrapped or stretched over
It's a due date
It's a skin walker
Yeah, definitely
A rake
A rake!
A rake.
Gotta do a rake on it.
Oh, shit.
Like, I feel like, I feel like...
Are you on a boat LD like like you look like you're on a boat like a cell
I beg this charity and now just jumped on the boat
I
Smells like curry and onions. Thank you. Come again somewhere. She's probably fucking
Thank you come again, okay, I'm cool
Depression and incense
The pressure women depression and incense. Wow. Yeah, we're all depressed
I mean just certain people come in the chat. It's just like it's just the downer like
Who are you who is that?
No, it was
He's talking from a potato life. He's from the New Jersey
Yes, you threw your trash on my lawn the other day say hello to James the cowboys
Yeah
I don't know. Yeah, I don't know him. I can't understand
My friend oh, yeah, you die alike. This is so different. Yeah
Yeah, yes, I did most of it. He took my goat. He didn't pay
I was I was I was I was at the summer 11
Yeah, I like 36B. Can I ask a secret question please?
Sleshy, Sleshy.
It's up who? It's up who?
It was Hafiz or Hamid or something.
I like 36B.
We like stop please. We like stop please.
We like stop please.
What is our host? Where is our host? Actually, where is our host?
We're making a song for CFS. Oh, that's right. Yes.
Oh, let me guess. Let me guess. AI. Let me talk. Let me talk. Let me talk.
God
I fucking hate it
Here we go again
And he's doing a fucking number of two
Oh yeah
What?
How are we far off?
Looking fine
and it's amplified
Amplified, right
Shad friends forever
Flying monkeys on the wire
Slinging into the sea
We set the stream on fire
Yeah, we fight life
Flying monkeys
No, no, we're putting flying monkeys on the wire
And it's better than fucking what Shan did
This is better
Yeah, like you mean
No, it's racist
There's no right there
Okay, there's no much
I like that. That's cool
Okay, why is two guys kissing I don't like that one
I don't know about this
I kinda like it
I don't even know like it
It was like two dudes kissing or whatever
That was the weird part
It was pretty racist
I don't know about this
I don't know what the fuck is this man, is that TV?
right there that change that change it to like a girl with long hair
you're not very homophobic something productive in your life guys thank you Joe
that was beautiful
that was racist but yay was it racist? I didn't even see that part
I think we're called flying monkeys.
Oh, my God.
You see races everywhere.
He did OK, except that there was the two dudes kissing.
Like, change one.
Yeah, Ziggy doesn't like that.
Oh, yeah.
He's obligated.
He's obligated to put that in there.
And apply it.
It's just part of the game.
To be honest, I don't belong to you people.
Start doing something productive in your life
To pump my gas
Why can't you give her $20? What even you talking right now?
Yeah, why are you being rude up here? This is like a CFF group. I'm talking about you people, you know
You people you people
Oh, here we go you people you mean you mean you people that shit and fucking public and wipe your fucking asshole with your hands and
What's your name?
Get some toilet paper.
Think of all the money they say on toilet paper there.
What's your toilet paper?
No, no, no.
I really want to know what's your name?
What is your name?
What's your name?
My name is Edesh Tomar.
Are you in America?
No.
Yes, you're not it. You're not in America. Okay. I know he's Jamaican. He's Jamaican
Yeah, he's a Minneapolis
Go get Lenore for me cuz you know that was the fourth greatest song ever you made
Sike, what are you doing right now? I don't even know what that is. What the hell? Oh, a cat. It's a cat. Oh, it's a cat
He's given the cat a bath
Are you like that mother cat? He's like the pussy. I'm surprised you don't lick your asshole like that
Where do you go
Disappearance
He got embarrassed
Aww, come on!
Come back!
Come back, psyche!
What a panel this is
Wow, CFF
CFF, maybe?
CFF All Stars
I mean, you know
Fat Grimace
I'm just watching the bingles and great rain things everything the CF up
Yeah, it is CF
CFF world
Can we add a you at the end
No, no
You
Joe Flacco did okay. Okay. Thanks Joe. You want to join I'm a you're in
In this time you're in
No, we don't let people that shit in rivers
Oh look at that, oh no you gotta change that, that part, that's the part you have to change.
Yeah, so you don't like that.
Yeah, it looks like two dudes kissing, that's fucking weird.
I can fix it for you, if you want me to
Ziggy can write a song
No, I can edit his song too
Oh, you can edit pictures
Yeah, I can edit this whole video
Well, you don't mean two guys kissing. I don't like that
Right back
Well, that's gay!
That's the only gay about that.
The hell with that! That's gay!
I'm still good live because I am who I am.
That's what he's doing.
and basically he pictures
yeah
that's a beautiful
he overcame the effect
weird
this is bad
by the way
alright
can we change subject guys
please
Have a couple ladies up here. What's another subject?
Yeah, like no hair
Come on man. Come on, dude
Scythe, you know what the hell you're doing quick. Come on come back. Will you come back and help us a little bit?
What the hell is he at?
No, we love psych, but he's doing bad
He's lying to Benny's DMs right now. Let him go
Benny oh shit. Oh, he's done with beta
Hey, if you have something to say say to my fucking face if I can Hindu bullshit bitch
I'm gonna go eat your god. He hasn't said a word
Loving bitch
And just study
You fucking cow worshipping bitch. Yeah, I'm 99 and a half years old. Thank I mean like I don't know
Who I don't know who she's talking about but like I love thick women. So
Maybe if you're talking about me, okay, I'm talking about that
That's so true, dude.
It's bad lighting, JT.
Don't you trust me brown or something?
Why are you gray?
He's so brown, he turned gray, yellow, yellow, I don't know how to explain it to him, I had to put that in front of everything, really?
No, not racism, no, no, no, not racism, alcohol, all-lism.
No, no, no, this guy over here puts Mexican in front of, I mean, why do you have to put Mexican?
Oh, no, no, wait, wait, because he's fucking racist. Yeah
Well, that's what JT was talking about
Yellow undertelling he has got jaundice or something. It's weird
Why you're fucking with yes stage four about
You didn't have fucking cancer. He lied about that shit. You did lie about
He's another one that lied about cancer jayme
Yeah
Vader lied about him having cancer who lies
That's crazy. Hey, Lars. Oh, I apologize to rain Vader Vader gives me cancer
I'm lying. I'm totally lying. He's never
I don't know
Fucking Tom Carlyer lied. Why are you calling us idiots? Are you serious? Wow?
Oh, you guys. Oh, you're looking for two years
Two years you hit him a nano going back. Yeah, that's why that's why he's not talking right now. He's embarrassed
Yes, the fucking talk shit from the side chat like a pussy bitch. What she looked like
Okay
Uh, you don't want to meet our boy, but but psyche. Why did you do that though?
But but psyche but psyche psyche I came up on your panel
Right, but but hey, no, no, I'm talking to you. You don't want to meet our boy though. You don't want to meet him
who
I'm talking about Vader will Durant
No, Bader she doesn't want the house. He does not want to meet Bader
Yeah, I am different people
Yeah, Jamie Rose. She'll only give you 43 minutes of her time
Jamie's Cowboys. She'll give you forever. Well Bader will own me. You know how good Bader is. He will only give you
15 minutes of your time for you to explain
Yeah, that's it. Are you talking about exactly? Sorry
That's right. Yeah
He'll cook you
Like there's black people like they're like they'll say yeah, I'm gonna cook you
Yeah, let's do better. Well, you're gonna cook me what like no, not me. No, they don't do
Later, we'll put they don't put you on a in a pan and stew you
He'll do right
Make beef stew out of you
That's what he does. He he slowly simmers
Come on
Why you have to talk about her not you
Don't trust that guy he's an Indian scammer. He'll scan you try to scam you out of your money
Yeah, you lied about cancer. What else could you lie about?
Hey
I mean if she's okay, like I would if if we got along I'm really like to put like an Indian bracelet on her
Is she that we got a word we got a word for that in English called handcuffs
He needs to be in handcuffs
Who are you talking about not you ring? I'm talking about I'm talking about her
I'm talking about this Indian piece of shit over there in the corner. Yeah, fuck it
He's busy wiping his bare ass before he fucking eats dinner
the
You throw your trash on my side of the river one more fucking time
I'm gonna come take a shit on your lawn. He speaks your language
Look at look at that. I got a year salary of a test in my wallet like
100 100 100 yeah, I got I got a year salary of tesh in my fucking wallet
You good, I'll pay you I'll pay you to go shit on Shannon's fucking lawn you fucking faggot
I like that
You come do it you come do a couple side quests for me, and I'll pay you in rupees like fucking Zelda
I literally like I would I'm up for fucking them somebody would ever want to fucking like pay half and half
Wish you were on Bruce half and half. What is the a prostitute? Yeah, no
No, it's a mean no to meet and fight like I would I was I'm fucking upset it before and
No one has ever like Vader won't do it
Vader's a busy young added mom
No
Hey, according to her it never happened, so she said you're the best you ever had
What do you expect compare that junkie Hollywood?
He probably he probably fucking nodded out on Fent while he was doing her
Damn
Did you see LD? Did you see psyche? He snatched Shannon's wig?
Why did you say it dude come on I knew someone was you see that you see that shit
She's like, oh my god, there's 50 people in chat. I'm so fucking funny. Huh? People know
Fucking
Ziggy Ziggy calm down rain calm your ass yourself down. Okay. No you come your ass your little fuck
Are you drunk?
Not what you would think that I would be.
But you better calm yourself.
You are always drunk, you know.
So what?
Why don't you go find your son, that's what you need to do, go find your son, that's what you need to do, go find your son, that's what you need to do, go find your son, that's what you need to do, go find your son, that's what you need to do, go find your son, that's what you need to do, go find your son, that's what you need to do, go find your son, that's what you need to do, go find your son, that's what you need to do, go find your son, that's what you need to do, go find your son, that's what you need to do, go find your son, that's what you need to do, go find your son, that's what you need to do, go find your son, that's what you need to do, go find your son, that's what you need to do, go find your son, that's what you need to do, go find your son, that's what you need to
You're like, why does he get to daughter?
I don't know if that's true, sir.
I'm an Aztec warrior, bitch.
You're getting scalped, bitch.
Dude, we didn't get along.
We didn't get along today.
And guess what? You're getting fucking scalped, okay?
Yeah, you're getting scotched, that's it.
to be honest and that's it you know yeah you know I don't even know what he was
saying what up what were you what were we talking about yeah why do you people you
don't even know seriously right because he's a weirdo he's a weirdo
But what's up? What's up? What's up? What are you going to say?
So it takes six Americans to speak to an Indian here.
I
Six six Americans to get to on it. Yeah, I got it
Hey, that's pretty funny. Hey, no, he made a joke. That's pretty fucking funny. That's pretty hilarious
Yeah, you're right. It only takes three British people to take over your whole fucking country
Yeah
And what the fuck are you doing and can I can I do one thing?
Well, where is our host number one
With the most
He doesn't like he doesn't host
I thought I was doing it. I thought I was lost in it, but it was hard, yeah. Hey, what's up? How's it going?
How you been? You alright?
I did. We watched the music earlier, me and Jan, and like everything was cool.
How was you and everything on the channel?
Yeah, it was fucking same old.
Oh my god. I saw a picture of Jan. She looks like a blonde pinky.
Well, thank you, but I also saw a picture of you and a little transvestite and that lucked weird
I'd strike you if you send that picture of me invader around
I
Just cuz he's wearing his mom's clothes and shit like that
That looked weird. What are you doing?
You guys are not in the right state of mind, you know
No, you're not in the way state of mind because you're not the channel owner and
JT is JT is the host
He's hosting right now. JT is hosting right now. What are you doing?
So I'm grateful these people
Obviously, yeah, we're getting close to Halloween and JT's hosting this stuff and it's really cool. I think I want to
Don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don
I swear to God, I don't understand a word that comes out of this guy's mouth
Do you guys look like Eggers, homeless people, you know?
See, you also look like Eggers
Oh, so, so, so
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, oh
Mega homeless people, is that what you said?
Dude, you live in a country where they bathe in little shit water
You talking about that?
Yeah
You wash your hair with cow shit and you're calling us poverty?
Dude!
You live in a country
And I want to tell you something too and and and I mean this like me starting off in my little dumb life. I
Fucking started off with nothing dude a trailer park and
grew up the band stuff went to the military and
Did all that kind of stuff man? So don't say what the fuck you're
I never thought I never thought about that. I never thought about that, but yeah, no
Don't don't don't don't don't don't say that we're fucking losers because I got fucking I bet you I have
Listen, I don't fucking
Buy high-end cars. No, no, no, I don't buy high-end cars
Okay, but I buy like low-end cars
And I do I do I deal with them the the the money that I've made
That's what I deal with
You're a fucking loser
Ziggy you could tow your car across the quarter mile quicker than fucking Hatesh on his donkey
Maybe I don't know. I'm not I'm not special though. You know, I'm not that
but
You know, don't say that about about people sometimes you don't know what the fuck
Talking to you know
Yeah, maybe I maybe I maybe I can maybe in in in defense I can buy you a goat. You want me to do that?
Well, he's got he's got two goats for milking and one for fucking
Nice
I know that's fucked up. No
No, no, no, it's most boring because you're you know, it's no no
It's that no I was there
It's most boring because you're the one that's fucking like whining right now
God, he had God if you ask it
Did you ask a test to see his toilet because you don't fucking have one?
Yeah, there's like a little room with a hole in the ground and a carton.
Well, you can't that's why you can't come on camera show is called it
Stolen Samsung government the government
Oh, yeah
He's on AOL 2.0 at least at least my woman fucking like shit. She's like
In a toilet
Okay
They they shit in the Ganges River. Yeah, they also bathed it dude
Honey like I'm being real I was there I was in Iraq and fucking it's a
Tigris Tiger's River
They, they, they, it's trash.
No bitch, you're not going to talk shit about Mexico, bitch.
Yeah, you don't care about it.
We bombed, we bombed Iraq back to the Stone Age
and there's still more advance than fucking India.
Fix your shit and get your shit wiped, bitch.
But I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I, I, I, dude,
that's, that's kind of one of the,
one of the things that fucking made me like, I was like, what?
Like I'm a I'm in I'm in Iraq and I'm looking at the Tigris River and
What they did was is that they threw their trash
Yeah, no, no, they threw the no, I'm telling I'm telling you
They threw every garbage every garbage plastic anything they threw it in the Tigris River
And it was like this polluted. Yeah, and like you the Euphrates was already full
Right whatever it was, but and I'm like, okay
so when I was
learning the Bible
The tiger server. No, no, hold on. Hold on a minute. Wait, wait, wait, man. Hold on. Give me a second
So I'm like when I was learning the Bible
Now I'm here. I'm at the Tigris
And it's like ugly, it's completely ugly and
then I was in a fucking
Copter and I was fucking flying over, you know, what was supposed to be
you know yeah the fucking Garden of Eden and I'm like all day and anything there
fuck that shit you know like I'm like fuck that no way
Fuck it. We're on to the game with these crank calls by the way these camcalls
So I love then you know I like that lady
Well, you know really you know you're really gonna like her whenever she goes on cam
Because she's gonna do
Yeah, she's no she's no she's actually going to go on cam on Halloween
Okay, I have a not subscribe to a channel yet, but I have seen you guys most sub what are you doing?
And care about you. She cares about yeah
Yeah, well sub man
Yeah
Who the hell said that?
That game has been over for like fuckin 12 hours
I know but they just started it for
Prime
It's a test screen sharing it for you I
Don't know why they don't play it till like 10 o'clock my time and Cali. I don't know why
Oh, you're in Cali. Okay. Yeah, I'm gonna get it. Yeah, what's your name?
AFC and MC is gonna be a hard division this year because Colts and you know Ravens and and chiefs
They're all like, I don't know. I think bills. Just they've lost a couple of games. So it's like it's not funny, buddy. Oh
JT I got I got a good gift
Wait for it
Yeah, I'm
Says it on what?
What careful careful you're gonna get spam calls. I've already gotten them all day. What's the point?
You're gonna get more
That's not JT was still here shit. I bet
Hey, I thought he's still here. No Goddy left
Goddy come on hurry up. Go back up here
Yeah, get up here mother you have to tell Goddy like get up here mother
if you guys
You're being attacked by new crew
At least you're here fucking I got
Gaudi said he was getting pizza
Rain I got a fucking cool ass tool for dude. I got a cool
Oh a tool nice
No, God, he just doesn't like you. That's all
Yeah, and I don't and I don't like you either
There you go
Fucking I don't fucking like a really cool democracy hitesh. That's some democracy
We're bringing democracy your way
Dude bro, I got her a fucking really cool fucking tool man. You you'll you'll be like, oh, that's cool
Joe can you believe the bears one the other day?
That's the bears the bears
Glad it was over the red
You know our division is NFC, so I was just like hoping that NFC. What is the NFC?
It's football NFC national football. Yeah
Little bitch fucking paying attention
I
Slap the hell out of you
Ziggy she just likes
If we need what fucking education
Fuck fuck you
And so is Katrina. So, you know, I just want to know what she say
Appropriate education
No
JT's woman. What did you say?
Oh
Ziggy, what?
I said Ziggy, Jamie just really likes football. What's wrong with that?
He is
He's wrong
Alright, nice thing
For God's sake, I don't want to hear yours
I will go for you
Like I don't understand what that guy's saying me neither
I don't know what you're doing
Like a sailor guy
I am on my ship and then I'm on my boat and then I'm in I don't know what you're doing. I don't know anything
Ziggy Jan is mine, you know
Oh, oh, that's all I understood Jan was mine. Yeah. Oh
Would you like to get a biggie she he just wants her for the chicken's cuz he hasn't eaten in three days
You know try try that
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I try try it
Just just like I'm told Vader you go and you try and
You guys know what I ate for my birthday a big fat juicy steak
Yeah, yeah, you don't have to compliment JT that way we get it
As long as I am here JT just said dummy kitesh jealous
Oh, no, I love Hatesh, by the way. He's one of my good friends
No, I'm I really
Hatesh is like one of my good friends. Hatesh is jealous because he wishes he could eat steak, too
But high-tech, you know, seriously high-tech. She's always been one of my good friends and he knows it and
Yeah, fuck up
No
No, don't say that man
No, don't say that trigger word
Yeah
He knows it man. I touch is one of my good people for real
You know he must have been one of the gherkas you served with
I
Okay
No, but I tell you she's fucking like a good dude. You're good dude. Your woman's a good person and
Fucking it's kind of what I remain here with that and that's pretty much what I want to do
There's one P.m. Yeah, you can't do that anymore
What do you mean? Why you better jobless anyway, right?
Bye-bye
We
That's not that's not high-tech though. It's not all of us can work for Microsoft support
Yeah, but that's not high-tech guys, that's not high-tech more like scam calls. No, that's yeah, no that there's
Yeah, that's not him
I know his voice and it's not him
Are we left haha cry about it bitch
Cheers bitch
Okay, all right
Okay
Do you know what?
Do what you do, but just don't be calling the LD a bitch right now. I didn't call him that I called to touch that
No, don't call Jan a bitch either
Didn't call her that I didn't even bring her up. You did and you actually did no I didn't
Made it. Oh, it's a test. It's a test that he was talking to her
Yeah, yeah
Yeah, but that wasn't him. That's not hot as it was low test
No, right. Yeah, I test is a real one. He wouldn't do that
He knows me. Yeah, he's a real one
No, seriously, that's not real high-touch hateful people really, okay
He was on that gut up in here and started insulting all of us. No, okay, let's let's get real
The dude that you guys keep thinking that it's high-touch
That's the guy that's on JCS and I can't remember his name
What's his name
I'm sure what's the name
That's not that's not well where's psyche I don't know yeah, I think God he's backstage is that a different person?
Yeah, they're totally two different people. Yes. That's what I'm trying to say
Like so you have like that dude up there with JC. That's not
That's not our dude and
Is
Dottie what it's got to give him back. You had to get his pizza remember
Is he backstage? I
Don't know
Yeah, I'm not sure
Wait a CFF panel that was fun
Yeah, we're always fun. Yeah, we are
Yeah, look at look at fucking
D man, he's glasses and everything. What are you going to just support for Halloween, LD?
employed
I'm gonna dress up as a nurse and go to work
That's cool. Oh, you get on with the like the suit not the suit, but uh, yeah
That's cool, man
What about you? Let's go to
What about
Rain, what are you doing for halloween?
I don't celebrate halloween
You don't celebrate halloween, okay
All right, why like is it like a religious thing?
Well that and like i don't know i feel like it's mostly mostly for kids. Yeah
Oh like it it's like a
Like you're really really okay. What about JT like does he celebrate?
No, no, you guys don't really celebrate it. Okay
What about what about the channel owner speed listen she just doesn't want to tell you no
I paint my face and I go and perform sacrifices
Stop!
I can't.
I will, I'm going to, I'm gonna pay myself as the quail and fucking get on this fucking,
I'm gonna turn my camera on. Wait, you forgot about Jamie, you forgot about Jamie, ask her.
So Halloween is like every day for me because it's like one of my favorite year besides Christmas,
but I've been in that accident so I'm still healing so it's gonna take a little bit of time
to to walk again a little bit better. Thanks. What kind of injuries do you have, Jamie?
Oh, so here's like lung and then the ribs are bruised really bad and then a concussion ongoing concussion and memory loss so I have to write things down and then so I have tuition around the ribs and so I need another couple of MRIs.
and I had to relearn how to walk, talk, eat again.
And like every day is a new day.
Whoa, she's perfect for you.
Ha ha, stop.
Ha ha.
That's what I'm trying to say.
Ziggy, I'll be, I'll be engaged.
Don't want to be mean to you.
We would have died in that wreck
because now it's an uphill battle.
And so I'm trying to figure everything out,
like I, you know, like where.
You know to go from here. So wait you you broke your ribs and the ribs
They're torn tissue really bad
So it's like they're healing
But it's taken a while to re-walk on that. I guess
Man, they don't even they don't even do like compresses anymore like there's no they don't tape you up
They don't do anything. They just leave your ribs the way they are
Like if you break your ribs don't even go to the hospital and get an x-ray because it's like they're not even gonna do anything for you
I've been trying to heal like, you know, I could still feel the pain
The socks
And then the PTSD at night cuz I got my days and like nighttime and what's the P?
Wait, wait, wait, what's the PTSD? What do you mean going back to the wreck of hollering and screaming from the chaos I sleep
Yeah, yeah, so there's late nights and saw me. I never like that was one thing that I've never had like is
Like the terror
Thoughts and you know, like I never had fucking PTSD man
I'll think I think it was because you know, I grew up like hunting and I grew up hunting and
You know and whatever
like something's coming through like the house or something
and it's just not me, it just takes me back to that night.
But then I don't have the whole thing
because in a trauma and like in like a something
that happens like right away,
you forget certain people, certain things.
And I'm trying to piece them back together. I'm learning my speech all over again. So it was like a really scary moment
You're learning it. Wait. Whoa. You're learning your actual speech over again. Yeah, that's crazy
That's crazy. Did you did you break your jaw or anything like that?
To the right and left. Yeah, really. Oh t.m.j. You got t.m.j. Yeah
Oh t.m.j. Yeah, that's fucked that's fucked up. Yeah
That's crazy. Like I mean I never went through that. Thankfully
Caught a dead no, no, I just want to say it like this like I cut a dead friend and whatever but I've never
Heard him say mom, you know and that thing
But I never I never like, you know put myself in that
mind frame of
I got a, you know, I can't get out of this or something, you know.
I think what sucks is that our independence has taken away from us.
So an Uber to take her far away is like 200 round trip for the doctor.
So I've been helping her and it's just a healing process and it's just like, how am I going to do that?
But the things I used to do and everything I have like, I have to relearn those again.
I think that's why all that's okay well then we learn yeah yeah and then the
things happen before it's just memory issues a little bit from the hit I
didn't know a concussion is
Like makes you sleepy and makes you like yeah, don't don't fall asleep with a concussion, please
Isn't it like it's supposed to be like 44 hours. Yeah. Yeah, it's very bad
Don't go to bed
We're stupid we go to bed after getting hit in the head
Well, that's what the doctor said but
What you don't have you don't have like a traumatic brain injury or anything. Do you a little bit?
He said yeah a little bit cuz I mean remembering people
clearly
Okay, I
Don't know whatever. Yeah, just do your thing
Do your thing. I don't really give a shit ever. What's up with you?
LD how you doing?
You're still drinking that
sugar water
Well, Ziggy
Yeah, LD just recently got engaged. Yeah, did you LD really? I really don't think he did. Yeah, do that. I mean my girl
No
Did you?
Yeah, yeah, it's actually real
Yeah, I bought her a ring. Okay. All right. Oh, well my god. Did you do what kind of ring?
like
18 carat rose gold. I don't know what carrots are like cannot tell you that
No, no, what what I did what I did was is I bought a
3500 dollar
Gold white gold
I don't even know what the fuck. I'm just like that looks pretty. I think that was cheaper, you know, that's how I am
Shout out to Meg's real one in the chat. You guys great people
Did you propose or like in your sister's wedding? No, I did it while we were
She already had the wedding wait wait wait
She already had the fucking wedding and you guys fucking invited me and I fucking said I'm not coming
Damn, man. Was it cool?
Had a good time. I got fucking wasted
Dude, was it cool?
Yeah, it was really nice dude. It was on the beach everything. Is that where you first at the no, no, no, no, no, no
I did it in Philly
Yeah, okay, I did it. I did at the hotel while we were in Philly no pictures
I'm not trying wait. I didn't have a photographer there like take pictures of it. No, like
I've got you know everything but like don't don't be me man like she's actually a cool fucking chick dude
Like I've talked to her before she's really cool, dude
They're building the house is the house almost built and shit
Yeah, yeah, dude the house is done
Fuck that's cool. That's the elder my sister. Yeah, my sister heard brand new houses built
That's fucking cool, dude. Yeah
Yeah, man
Dude, I talked to her, you know, whenever I see her and yeah, me me too me, too
Well, obviously
Whenever I see her
Yeah, but it was it was a nice wedding man. It was you know cool. We did a good time
Yeah, I wanted to fucking go, but I'm not cuz I don't know her, you know
I don't know her
Yeah, I was gonna invite you, but I already had a date so you know
See, he is actually funny guys. Come on, JT. He's hilarious man. Come on. Get
But he's fucking funny. Come on
What are you talking about Ziggy JT's not even here. Yeah, JT's not here. I thought it was here. I'm sorry
Okay. All right. Well, I'm sorry
Dropped out already like God. He's okay
No, well, no, I'm used to it like his woman always jumps on me. Oh, it's cuz he never looks at his phone
Yeah, right. That's true. And
She his woman is close to my woman and she's always like
So I mean like what the fuck are you doing? That's what she's yeah, I know what you're doing
Taking like an hour
Who got he yeah, he was waiting on pizza
Oh, shit. Oh, he's oh, he's definitely Italian
Is it coming back?
Oh D. What the fuck are you doing? What's the music or something?
No, it's like panel. I'm not gonna play music. Oh
When I come back you see
That's like a full meal
Wait like in the full meal the fuck
Hey guys, I'm gonna go take care. Yeah, I think I gotta I gotta go to the vet man
I guess well, I gotta wake up kind of early
Wish the baby Duke. Yeah. Yeah, we're getting them. We're getting the biop feed on tomorrow
And I'll figure out if it's benign or malignant, you know, if it's some foam or whatever, but
I don't know about this. What the fuck you got a tumor or something
It's I don't know if it's I listen. What do I know? I'm not a medical professional
It's well. Yeah, you are you're a fucking nurse
It's like it's like a mass and it's right under his arm
Hey, and with my knowledge, you know with a mass under the armpit. That's typical typically a lymph node, so
No, I'm really afraid it's lymphoma
So I'm taking him to the vet to go get it looked at and biopsy tomorrow, and I'm praying to God. It's not lymphoma
Yeah, I hope no, dude
good boy I hope not good boy yeah I love yeah I can't yeah you've laying on the
side that it's on right now but it's a it's like a good like half inch diameter
mass and the past couple days I've been putting like hot compresses on it to
relieve it
But it's just been getting redder and pinker and I just I don't know
Well then what you're kind of describing is you know like one of my buddies man like I'm not trying to be gross girls
but
Like showed me you know like it was
Testicle was like weirdly
You know and I'm like
Bro go and get that checked
Yeah, no, no, dude. I won't do that man. Fuck that dude. He died of
testicular cancer
Well, it's like a lot of the a lot of your lymph nodes are in your groin and also in your armpit and your neck
No, no, no, no what what you're pointing that right now
It's from your neck down all the way through your armpit down through your side and
All that yeah, yeah, they're your lymph node
So me personally I'm like well is he fighting an infection because you can have like a swollen lymph node from an infection
I'm like, yeah, I have fever and like so I don't think it's an infection
But, I don't know, I don't know if I'm taking him to the vet tomorrow, you know, I just don't know, I'm sad man.
He's eating good, he's drinking good, he's shitting and pissing good, I mean, I'm just hoping it's a benign mass in his armpit, it's just the location is what scares me is that it's so close to his armpit.
Right, well, I think you're thinking inside like it's close to the heart.
And that's not it's not a cardiac issue. It's it would be cancer, but I'm it's the lymph nodes
You know when your body is fighting something your lymph nodes are working to fight
Whatever you have an infection or bacteria
so
You might have a swollen lymph node, you know, so that sucks. Yeah. Yeah, we're wishing the best for Duke
Thank you. I appreciate it. Cheers to Duke
My fucking let me let me show you him home. He's sleeping right now, but where are you my baby boy?
My baby. Oh
Look at that dog go the teeth. Look at the teeth
Yeah, there you go
My baby boy, it's my baby boy
And it's so sad man because the fiance had to put the female greyhound down like six months ago
So it's like so no
Serious
Yeah, my girl had to put the the female down like six months ago
So it's just it's just so sad and I'm like I'm praying it's just praying dude
It's like I want a couple more years at it. I really do
Yeah, yeah, we're all praying for do I was there I was there
Before like whatever you were hanging out with you know, I
Do you want me to say the name? I don't care
okay
fucking
retard blonde
fucking and you had
Duke there and
That was awesome
Well, I there's been a lot of retarded blondes. I've hung well, you know who I'm talking to I did you know who I'm talking about
I didn't bring I didn't bring Duke with me to Calif. I didn't want it
I didn't want them to know that's what I'm trying to do here. Oh
You mean vegan you mean vegan. Yeah
Yeah, right
She's not retarded. She's just vegan. She's pretty retarded and fucking you had the dog there a lot
Yeah, I lived I lived there. I lived with I lived with vegan in Arizona
Mm-hmm, right. I know her dog her dog. I know that that's why I didn't want to say it, but I
This is for you this is for your health cheers for your health
Oh, dude, by the way, I have a question because I think I'm gonna go there
What the fuck was that called were you guys went to that fucking?
That fuck was that called
It was like where no one like
In Arizona, I'm pretty sure yeah, it was
The fucking one place where you could just go and just nothing that thing pretty sure that's
A place where you went to Arizona and nothing right. Yeah
Sounds like Arizona
Yeah, no, it was like
No, no, no, it was like no it was like stone something or
Something I don't know man. I've never been there. I don't remember
All the hippies go there. There's nothing there
That's I don't know. I'm not a hippie
Well, you kind of were but
Mmm
What the fuck is that called my god
Who's my boy? It was like an old military place, man and fucking
it was
Desicrated basically and it was just a bunch of fucking
Concrete concrete something in Arizona
Don't I really don't remember dude. I remember yeah, man. You don't remember that. I drank my memory away
mmm
It was like it was like concrete
something Oh
Flab city. Yes. Yes. That's it
Yes
We never while I was with vegan we never went to slab city and I think flab cities in California actually
No, you were there. I watched you. Is it I never I never been to slab city. I'm pretty sure
For yeah, pretty sure that you were at fucking slab city
No, I never went there's only like three hours for us Reno. So what Reno, Nevada?
Well, there was something where you were in something like that and then the dog
And then like you were pissed at somebody I don't remember man
Whatever. No, I brought I brought the dog on the RV when we went to the RV on calis in, California
I'm never been there
Well, anyway guys city slap city though. You were there though, right?
No, I've never I never been to slap city. I'm pretty sure you were
I mean you obviously know better than I do so
No, no, maybe I'm wrong. I'm sure I'm wrong
I thought you were
Yeah, but
Cuz they went to a slab city and I'm pretty sure that's where the dog right like you went there
LA we were on the RV in LA and stuff
Right, okay, okay cheese and minnet and all those people
What's the net the one now? I guess making out with BG and DGF
Oh shit. I heard I heard someone told me someone told me today that Gucci's had a baby
the
I guess I don't know. I don't know
So where's our host that by the way
I thought we're a tarot channel
I
Said
Let's do a Mason
Okay, okay stupid
10,000 questions
Okay, well, whatever you guys take care. Hey, man, go see in the LB you too, man. Have a good night
See you later. Bye. Bye